Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Doug Henwood on Social Security and Private Pension Crisis; Henry Foner Interviews Catherine Roberts on Social Security; Martha Saunders on Divestment from Corporations Supporting Israeli Occupation [2005-042], 2005-08-28 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_17)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz and Lynne Sharon Schwartz on The Writing on the Wall, Counterpoint [2005-080], 2005-08-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_47)
- Liza Featherstone, Pat Purcell, and Bill Serrin on Wal-Mart Efforts to Break into New York City Market and United Food and Commercial Workers (UFCW) AFL-CIO Split; Workmen's Circle's Jewish Social Justice Conference with Dara Silverman [2005-043], 2005-09-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_18)
- Michael Zweig [2005-001], 2005-09-07 (Box 23, Item 718_0989)
- Brian Klug on UK Response to July Bombings; Rabbi Guy Austrian and Dr. Mohammed Sahloul on Muslim Charities; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Lynne Sharon Schwartz on The Writing on the Wall [2005-045], 2005-09-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_19)
- Donna Nevel Remembers Rabbi Balfour Brickner; Kathy Engel on Rebuilding New Orleans; Jewish Responses to Katrina with Nathaniel Popper; Wayne Barrett on NYC's Mayoral Primary [2005-044], 2005-09-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_20)
- Phyllis Bennis on Iraq Exit Strategy and UN Summit; Gregg Bordowitz on The AIDS Crisis is Ridiculous and Other Writings [2005-065], 2005-09-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_21)
- James Besser, Breaching the Church-State Levees in New Orleans; Ira Sachs on Forty Shades of Blue; Khaled Hroub on Hamas [2005-066], 2005-10-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_22)
- Hany Abu-Assad on Paradise Now [2005-012], 2005-10-06 (Box 18, Item 718_0753)
- Hany Abu-Assad on Paradise Now [2005-055], 2005-10-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_42)
- Marathon: Stephen Bronner, Chip Berlet, Hour 2 [2005-068], 2005-10-16 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_23)
- Interviews with Chip Berlet, Stephen Bronner, and Mark Levin [2005-067], 2005-10-16 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_24)
- Omar Barghouti on Academic Boycott [2005-035], 2005-10-23 (Box 19, Item 718_0776)
- Haim Yavin [2005-054], 2005-10-28 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_41)
- Priscilla Gonzalez from Center for Immigrant Families; Campaign Against Torture with Rabbi Brian Walt; Hany Abu-Assad on Paradise Now [2005-046], 2005-10-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_25)
- Elizabeth Loeb on GSOC Strike at CUNY; Daphne Golan-Agnon on 10th Anniversary of Rabin Assassination; Henry Foner Interviews David Margolick on Beyond Glory [2005-047], 2005-11-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_26)
- Selections from Beyond the Pale 10th Anniversary [2005-076], 2005-11-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_39)
- 10th Anniversary Excerpts: Prayer for NY (Kushner), Judith Malina, Roya Hakakian, Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Music [2005-075], 2005-11-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_40)
- Live Broadcast: Lorin Sklamberg and Lisa Gutkin (Klezmatics), Basya Schechter (Pharaoh's Daughter), Abe Velez (Hip Hop Hoodios), Alex Kontorovich (Klez Dispensers), Sarah Aroeste; "A Prayer for New York" Performed by Ben Shenkman and Lynne Cohen; Michelle Goldberg, Author of Kingdom Coming; Ruth Knafo-Setton, Author of The Road to Fez; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Author of The Color of Jews, Disc 1 [2005-059], 2005-11-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_50)
- Live Broadcast: Lorin Sklamberg and Lisa Gutkin (Klezmatics), Basya Schechter (Pharaoh's Daughter), Abe Velez (Hip Hop Hoodios), Alex Kontorovich (Klez Dispensers), Sarah Aroeste; Yifat Susskind; Roya Hakakian, Author of Journey from the Land of No; Judith Malina Readings of Grace Paley's Work, Disc 2 [2005-059], 2005-11-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_51)
- Marathon: Beyond the Pale 10th Anniversary Excerpts, Hour 1, 2005 November 13; 2006 February 12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_66)
- Michael Sorkin of Against the Wall; Seth Tobocman and Terry Berkowitz on Three Cities Against the Wall Exhibition; Dara Silverman on Unite-Progressive Jewish Coalition [2005-049], 2005-11-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_27)
- Examining the Real Agenda of the Religious Far Right Conference (April 29-30, 2005): Karen Armstrong's "Fundamentalism: The Fear and the Rage" Talk; Chip Berlet's "Millenialist and Apocalyptic Influences on Dominionism" Talk [2005-048], 2005-11-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_28)
- Chip Berlet at CUNY Grad Center, 4/29/05 [2005-051], 2005-11-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_36)
- Craig Unger on the Religious Right and His Book American Rapture; Larry Cohler-Esses on Salvation Army Case; Mark Pelavin on Abraham Foxman and Eric Yoffie Remarks on Christian Right [2005-069], 2005-12-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_29)
- Ervand Abrahamian on Iran; Leslie Cagan on the "Murtha" Effect; Joachim Neugroschel [2005-070], 2005-12-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_30)
- Michel Warschawski on Upheaval in Israeli Politics; Sen. Liz Krueger on US Budget and Tax Cuts; Jewltide Music Groups [2005-072], 2005-12-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_31)
- Michelle Goldberg, Rabbi Michael Lerner, and Alisa Solomon on the War Against Christmas; Phyllis Bennis on the Iraqi Elections [2005-071], 2005-12-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_32)
- The War Against Christmas with Alisa Solomon [2005-052], 2005-12-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_34)
- Joann Sfar, Author of The Rabbi's Cat [2005-073], 2005-12-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_37)
- Beinin [2015-022], circa 2006-2007 (Box 20, Item 718_1016)
- Udi Ofer on NSA Surveillance and Patriot Act; Gideon Aronoff on HR 4437 and Immigration Reform; Neve Gordon on Sharon's Exit, 2006-01-08 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_61)
- Bruce Shapiro on Alito Nomination; Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Tribute with Susannah Heschel; Excerpts from "Why I Oppose the War in Vietnam" Speech, 2006-01-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_63)
- Michael Wex on Born to Kvetch; Abramoff Scandal with Barry Yeomans and Nicholas Confessore; Bearing the Unbearable Film Festival with Danae Elon and Dorothea Von Moltke, 2006-01-22 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_62)
- Jeremy Leaming on Proselytizing at Air Force Academy Backlash; Harold Meyerson on Immigration Reform and Context; Steve Rendall on Venezuela's President Chavez and His Allegedly Anti-Semitic Speech, 2006-01-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_64)
- Hamas Victory with Rabab Abdulhadi, Rashid Khalidi, and Michel Warschawski, 2006-02-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_65)
- Israel Forum, "What Happens Now? Israel and the Palestinians After Gaza, Sharon, and Hamas" with Gideon Levy, Christopher Hitchens, Elias Khoury, and Tony Judt, 2006-03-09 (Box 19, Item 718_0780)
- Gideon Levy, 2006-03-09 (Box 19, Item 718_0788)
- Gideon Levy, 2006-03-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_58)
- Palestinian Anti-Terrorism Act with James Besser and Josh Ruebner; Gideon Levy Interview, 2006-03-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_82)
- Rachel Back at New Israel Fund, 2006-03-19 (Box 19, Item 718_0782)
- Anti-Semitism on the Left with Chip Berlet and Dara Silverman; Rachel Back on Language and Poetry, Reading from With an Iron Pen, 2006-03-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_83)
- Eyal Press, 2006-03-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_74)
- Phyllis Bennis, 2006-03-25 (Box 19, Item 718_0785)
- Phyllis Bennis on Stephen Walt and John Mearsheimer Essay, "The Israel Lobby", 2006-03-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_94)
- The Israel Lobby and U.S. Foreign Policy with Phyllis Bennis and Joel Beinin; US Foreign Policy, Iran, and Israel with Ervand Abrahamian, 2006-03-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_84)
- Neve Gordon on Israeli Elections; Marcie Cohen Ferris on Matzoh Ball Gumbo, 2006-04-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_85)
- Joseph Stiglitz et al. on The True Cost of the Iraq War; Rashid Khalidi and Jane Arraf, 2006-04-03 (Box 19, Item 718_0793)
- Joyce Antler and Marla Brettschneider on The Goldbergs, 2006-04-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_95)
- Frederique Pressman on Demonstrations in France; Kevin Appleby on Conference of Catholic Bishops, 2006-04-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_86)
- Amira Hass, 2006-04-11 (Box 19, Item 718_0789)
- Stanley Hordes on To the End of the Earth: A History of the Crypto-Jews of New Mexico; Omar Barghouti on Palestinian Academic Boycott; Roger Bowen and Susannah Heschel on William Sloane Coffin, 2006-04-16 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_87)
- Omar Barghouti Academic Boycott, 2006-04-16 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_90)
- Ruth Messinger on 4/30 Darfur Rally, 2006-04-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_96)
- Mitchell Plitnick on Jewish Silence on Iraq War; Ruth Messinger on 4/30/2006 Rally to Save Darfur; Israel Forum, "What Happens Now? Israel and the Palestinians After Gaza, Sharon, and Hamas" with Tony Judt and Christopher Hitchens, 2006-04-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_88)
- Tony Judt and Christopher Hitchens at Israel Forum, "What Happens Now? Israel and the Palestinians After Gaza, Sharon, and Hamas", 2006-04-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_97)
- Ruth Messinger on Save Darfur Rally, 2006-04-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0797)
- Tiffany Shlain on Her Film The Tribe; Mireille Silcoff and Lara Vapnyar on Guilt & Pleasure Literary Journal; Bob Hercules on Film Forgiving Dr. Mengele, 2006-04-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_89)
- Documentary Drama with Igal Ezraty, Alisa Solomon, etc. at the CUNY Graduate Center, 2006-05-01 (Box 19, Item 718_0794)
- Domestic Workers Bill of Rights with Earline Brown and Sarah Strnad; Aaron Taub, Author of The Inscrutable Psalm; Daniel Sieradski, Founder of jewschool.org, 2006-05-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_73)
- Jim Besser and Josh Ruebner; Intro with Music and Other Music, 2006-05-10 (Box 19, Item 718_0792)
- Nathaniel Popper on Labor Exploitation at Kosher Slaughterhouses in Postville, Iowa; Laila El-Haddad on Her Blog, Raising Youssef; Blu Greenberg on Gett and Agunah, 2006-06-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_75)
- Rabbi Brian Walt and Rabbi Arik Ascherman of Rabbis for Human Rights, 2006-06-06 (Box 19, Item 718_1019)
- Michael Massing on Israel Lobby; Liz Holtzman on CIA Knowledge of Eichmann and Other Nazis' Locations after WWII, 2006-06-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_77)
- Jeffrey Shandler on Adventures in Yiddishland with Alisa Solomon, 2006-06-15 (Box 19, Item 718_0779)
- Rabbi Menachem Creditor, 2006-06-21 (Box 19, Item 718_0783)
- Dr. Mona El-Farra, Laila El-Haddad, and Phyllis Bennis on Israeli Invasion of Gaza and Arrest of Hamas Leaders, 2006-07-01 (Box 19, Item 718_0791)
- Dr. Mona El-Farra, Laila El-Haddad, and Phyllis Bennis on the Israeli Invasion of Gaza and Arrest of Hamas Leaders, 2006-07-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_78)
- Nidal Ibrahim of Arab-American Institute; Democratic Primary Candidate for Senate in Connecticut, Ned Lamont; Hisham Melhem on Syria, 2006-07-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_80)
- Reza Aslan on Iran's Role in Lebanon and His Book No God But God; Adi Dagan on Israel; Rabbi Michael Lerner on the American Jewish Community and the War in Lebanon, 2006-08-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_81)
- Sidney Blumenthal on How Bush Rules: Chronicles of a Radical Regime; Gideon Levy on Gaza and Lebanon War; Cole Krawitz with Jennifer Miller of Circus Amok, 2006-08-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_79)
- Rabbi Jill Jacobs on New Orleans Activism; Beejhay Barhany on Ethiopian Jewish Film Festival, BINA; Jonathan Tasini, Democratic Senate Primary Challenger to Hillary Clinton, 2006-08-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_101)
- Labor Day Discussion with Bruce Raynor and Stephen Lerner; Walter Ruby on Assembly Race in Brighton Beach, 2006-09-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_99)
- Phyllis Rodriguez of 9/11 Families for a Peaceful Tomorrow; Konnie Chameides on Young, Jewish, and Left; 11th Congressional District Primary in Brooklyn with Candidates David Yassky and Chris Owens, 2006-09-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_102)
- Chris Monaco on Moses Levy of Florida: Jewish Utopian and Antebellum Reformer, 2006-09-15 (Box 19, Item 718_0786)
- Chris Monaco on Moses Levy of Florida: Jewish Utopian and Antebellum Reformer, 2006-09-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_92)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Jeffrey Shandler on Adventures in Yiddishland, 2006-09-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_91)
- Sasha Abramsky on Voting Rights; Jeffrey Shandler on Adventures in Yiddishland with Alisa Solomon; Leslie Cagan on Anti-war Demonstration, 2006-09-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_103)
- "Under Siege: American Democracy in the Age of Bush" with Katha Pollitt, Patricia Williams, Elizabeth Holtzman, and Laura Flanders, 2006-09-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_53)
- Freida Lee Mock on Wrestling with Angels; Excerpts from "Under Siege: American Democracy in the Age of Bush" Panel at Brooklyn College Book Festival with Laura Flanders, Patricia Williams, and Elizabeth Holzman, 2006-09-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_104)
- Dena Hammerstein on My Name is Rachel Corrie; David Zellnik on Ariel Sharon Stands at the Temple Mount and Dreams of Theodor Herzl; Abe Velez Interviews Jeffrey Lewis with Live Music, 2006-10-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_105)
- Abe Velez Interview with Jeffrey Lewis, 2006-10-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_93)
- Antony Beevor and Luba Vinogradova on A Writer at War, 2006-10-12 (Box 19, Item 718_0787)
- Hanon Reznikov reading from Vasily Grossman's A Writer at War, 2006-10-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_55)
- Antony Beevor, editor and translator of Vasily Grossman's A Writer at War, 2006-10-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_57)
- Marathon Special on Vasily Grossman with Judith Malina, Hanon Reznikov, Antony Beevor, and Robert Chandler, Disc 1, 2006-10-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_106)
- Marathon Special on Vasily Grossman with Judith Malina, Hanon Reznikov, Antony Beevor, and Robert Chandler, Disc 2, 2006-10-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_107)
- Scott Ritter and Seymour Hersh on Iran at Ethical Culture Institute (Special Sponsored by The Nation), 2006-10-16 (Box 19, Item 718_0784)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interview with Robin Becker, 2006-10-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_60)
- Mark Crispin Miller on 2004 Elections and His Book Fooled Again; 2006 Mid-Term Elections with Jennifer Siegel, 2006-10-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_68)
- Ruchama Marton of Israel Committee for Residency Rights, 2006-11-02 (Box 19, Item 718_0795)
- Scott Ritter on Iran's Nuclear Programs, US War Plans, and His Book Target Iran; Mona El-Farra on the Humanitarian Crisis in Gaza; Michael Ratner on the Military Commission Act, 2006-11-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_76)
- Robin Becker; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz; Aziz Abu Sarah; Parents Circle: Families Forum, 2006-11-12 (Box 19, Item 718_0796)
- Ann Snitow Remembers Ellen Willis; John Green on the Evangelical Vote; Wendy Weiser on 2006 Elections; Nahanni Rous on the Film Encounter Point, 2006-11-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_69)
- Adrienne Rich at Center for LGBTQ Studies (CLAGS) Annual Kessler Lecture, 2006-11-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_54)
- Muriel Rukeyser Special with Jan Heller Levi, Suzanne Gardinier, and Adrienne Rich, 2006-11-26 (Box 19, Item 718_0781)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Jody Rosen on Jewface, 2006-11-26 (Box 19, Item 718_0790)
- Suzanne Gardinier (Track 1); Adrienne Rich (Track 2); Hugh Seidman (Track 3); Jan Heller Levi (Track 4); Interview (Track 5), 2006-11-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_52)
- Rukeyser Tribute Panel: Jan Heller Levi Interview, 2006-11-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_56)
- Muriel Rukeyser Special with Jan Heller Levi, Suzanne Gardinier, and Adrienne Rich, 2006-11-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_70)
- Jim Hoberman on Borat; Vincent Panama Alba on Shooting of Sean Bell by NYPD, 2006-12-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_71)
- Alisa Solomon Interview with Jody Rosen on Jewface, 2006-12-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_59)
- Esther Kaplan and Abe Velez on FCC; Jed Abrahamian on Iran; Alisa Solomon Interviews Jody Rosen on Jewface, 2006-12-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_72)
- Brian Walt of Rabbis for Human Rights; Lisa Jervis and Andi Zeisler on the 10th Anniversary of Bitch Magazine; Joann Sfar on The Rabbi's Cat, 2006-12-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_98)
- Rashid Khalidi [2015-018], circa 2007-2011 (Box 20, Item 718_1013)
- Rabbi Marc Gellman [2015-021], circa 2007-2014 (Box 20, Item 718_1018)
- Geoffrey Aronson on Israeli Settlement Expansion; Sara Roy and Daniel Sievadsky on AJC Report on Anti-Semitic Jews, 2007-01-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_124)
- Rev. Osagyefo Sekou on 1/27 March and Martin Luther King, Jr.; Jim Hoberman and Richard Pena on Jewish Film Festival; Michael Ratner Remembers Bob Boehm; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Remembers Tillie Olsen, 2007-01-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_131)
- Rashid Khalidi for 2/4/2007 Marathon, 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_112)
- Ali Abunimah on One Country: Introduction and Reading (Track 1), Interview (Track 2), 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_115)
- Ruchama Marton, 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_123)
- Marathon: Ali Abunimah on One Country: A Bold Proposal to End the Israeli-Palestinian Impasse; Rashid Khalidi on The Iron Cage: The Story of the Palestinian Struggle for Statehood; Dr. Ruchama Marton on the Israeli Committee for the Right of Residency; Dr. Tarik Ramahi on Efforts to Enter Israel, Disc 2, 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_166)
- Marathon Special, 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_169)
- Interview with Shulamit Aloni on Jimmy Carter's Book Palestine: Peace Not Apartheid, 2007-02-11 (Box 19, Item 718_0805)
- Rep. Jerrold Nadler on the New Congress; Ed Case on Jewish Population Surveys; Rebecca Manski on Negev Development Plans, 2007-02-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_167)
- Shulamit Aloni and Steven Friedman on Apartheid and Israel, 2007-02-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_116)
- Neil Baldwin on Mitt Romney's Presidential Candidacy Announcement; Shulamit Aloni and Steven Freedman on Apartheid and Israel; James Shapiro on Theater for a New Audience Productions of The Merchant of Venice and The Jew of Malta, 2007-02-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_168)
- Phyllis Bennis on Iran: How Likely is War?; Steven Beeber on The Heebie-Jeebies at CBGBs: a Secret History of Jewish Punk, 2007-02-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_163)
- Peter Miller on The Internationale, 2007-03-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_121)
- Udi Aloni on Effort by Israeli Consulate in Paris to Prevent His Film Forgiveness from Opening at the Israeli Film Festival; Sarita Gupta and Sheldon Freedman on the Employee Free Choice Act; Michael Weinstein on With God on Our Side: One Man's War Against an Evangelical Coup in America's Military, 2007-03-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_155)
- Peter Miller on Sacco and Vanzetti, 2007-03-11 (Box 19, Item 718_0808)
- Sue Udry on Anti-war Proposals in Congress and 3/18 Demonstration in New York City; Julie Wiener on Her In the Mix Column; Iver Bernstein on New York Divided: Slavery and the Civil War Exhibition, 2007-03-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_170)
- Eric Sawyer on Act-Up's 20th Anniversary; Alexander Nowak and Atina Grossman on Germany's Re-naturalization Program; Andre Schiffrin on A Political Education: Coming of Age in Paris and New York, 2007-03-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_165)
- J.J. Goldberg, 2007-03-21 (Box 19, Item 718_0813)
- Tanya Reinhardt Remembrance; J.J. Goldberg on American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) Conference and Vice President Cheney; Nan Rubin Interviews Michael Dorf; Abe Valez Interviews Frank London, 2007-03-25 (Box 19, Item 718_0799)
- J.J. Goldberg on Cheney's AIPAC Speech, 2007-03-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_113)
- Remembering Tanya Reinhardt; J.J. Goldberg on Dick Cheney's Speech at the Annual AIPAC Assembly; Michael Dorfman on the Downtown Jewish Cultural Scene; Frank London on the Klezmatics' Emmy Award for their Woody Guthrie CD, 2007-03-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_184)
- Peter Miller on His Documentary Sacco and Vanzetti, 2007-04-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_120)
- Peter Miller on His Documentary Sacco and Vanzetti; Gerald Horne on The Final Victim of the Blacklist and The Color of Fascism, 2007-04-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_164)
- Phyllis Bennis on Riyadh Summit; Rachel Kahn-Troster on Admission of LGBTQ to the Jewish Theological Seminary; Alicia Svigals on Her Series at The Stone, 2007-04-08 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_162)
- Chris Hedges on American Fascists: The Christian Right and the War on America; Annette Ezekiel, Leader of the Band Golem, 2007-04-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_161)
- Scott Sherman and Rashid Khalidi on The New York Sun at Five Years; Natasha Winegar and Anderson Fils-Aime on New York is Our Home Campaign; Laurel Reuter on Los Desaparecidos Exhibition, 2007-04-22 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_159)
- Sarah Henry and Moe Fishman on Fighting Fascism: New York and the Spanish Civil War; Yousef Jabareen on The Future Vision of the Palestinian Arabs in Israel; Yael Lehrer Interview, 2007-04-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_158)
- Peter Miller on The Internationale, Part 1, 2007-04-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0818)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Joyce Antler on You Never Call! You Never Write!, 2007-04-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0822)
- Gail Levin on Becoming Judy Chicago; Seymour Lachman on Three Men in a Room; Rachel Leon on Reforming New York State's Dysfunctional Government System, 2007-05-06 (Box 19, Item 718_0817)
- Gail Levin on Becoming Judy Chicago; Seymour Lachman on Three Men in a Room; Rachel Leon on Reforming New York State's Dysfunctional Government System, 2007-05-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_157)
- The Internationale with Peter Miller, Part 2, 2007-05-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_152)
- Marathon Special on The Internationale with Peter Miller (Partial), Part 1, 2007-05-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_156)